

SalehinChowdhury

Hs 360, Rd 5,
Mirpur DOHS
01715 006121
01711 400111
salehinchowdhury@yahoo.com

ABOUT ME

I am expert on Global Brand Communications, Also have exposure on Branding Local Products and Services, have versatile experience on all segments of ATL and BTL Communications, along with B2B and B2C background in terms of Product, Service and Social Branding. I have special skills on Startup ventures Brand Formulation with cost effectiveness and high integrity.

EDUCATION

(2010 - 2012)

MBA (MAJOR IN MARKETING)

AIUB

(recipient of 'Magna Cum Laude Award of Academic Excellence')

(2000 - 2005)

B. Sc. in COMPUTER SCIENCE AIUB

SALEHIN CHOWDHURY

Head – Brand & Communications Runner Automobiles Limited

EXPERIENCE

(2017-Present)

HEAD of BRAND & COMMUNICATIONS

RUNNER AUTOMOBILES LIMITED

Planning a complete Communications Journey for a leading Local 2 Wheeler and 3 wheeler brand and to create campaigns (2016 – 2017)

HEAD OF MARKETING

MANGO DIGITAL LTD. & SECURELIFE LIMITED (BENGAL GROUP)

Planning a complete Communications Journey for a leading Local cellphone brand and to create Communications and Sales Strategy for a Security Guard Supplier Company.

(2015 - 2016)

HEAD OF BRAND COMMUNICATIONS, PR & MARKETING

CANADIAN UNIVERSITY OF BANGLADESH

To Build a world class University Brand with State of Art Campus

(2014 - 2015)

MANAGER, BRAND & MARKETING

THE PREMIER BANK LIMITED

To take the Second Generation Bank's Brand journey to the Next level

(2013 - 2014)

INCHARGE. BRAND & MARKETING

JAMUNA GROUP LIMITED

Launching of Jamuna Electronics & Automobiles, SuperMall & Jamuna Television

(2011 - 2013)

DEPUTY MANAGER, BRAND COMMUNICATIONS & MARKETING

THE CITY BANK LIMITED

Has handled American Express Brand in Bangladesh for long Also worked for PR, Outdoors, Events & General Banking Branding For the esteemed Brand

(2007 - 2011)

EXECUTIVE, MARKETING

BANGLACAT

Many of the elements of the Brand skeleton of Caterpillar, Bangladesh Was initiated by me

REFERENCES

Mr. Mashrur Arefin- Additional Managing Director, The City Bank Limited

Chowdhury Nafeez Sarafat- Chairman, Canadian University of Bangladesh

K A M Mazedur Rahman, Ex-MD, The Premier Bank Limited